<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rtcc>
	<LoaderMax name="content" prependURLs="rtcc_web_assets/videos/">
		<section name="Proactive Policing">
			<VideoLoader name="section11" icon="step1" enabler="1" url="Scenario1_Video1.f4v" wait="5" autoPlay="false" ><![CDATA[Sunday mid-afternoon: Nearby sensors detect gunfire at a park bustling with families and pedestrians.  An immediate alert is sent to the Real-Time Intelligence Console operator.]]></VideoLoader>
			<VideoLoader name="section12" icon="step1" enabler="1" url="Scenario1_Video2.f4v" wait="3" autoPlay="false" ><![CDATA[On the Real-Time Intelligence Console, the exact location of the alleged incident appears on a map.]]></VideoLoader>
			<VideoLoader name="section13" icon="step2" enabler="1" url="Scenario1_Video3.f4v" wait="3" autoPlay="false" ><![CDATA[The map also displays the nearest patrol units, police officers and surveillance cameras.]]></VideoLoader>
			<VideoLoader name="section14" icon="step3" enabler="7" url="Scenario1_Video4.f4v" wait="4" autoPlay="false" ><![CDATA[The Real-Time Crime Center uses its radio console "MCC7100" to call several units immediately to the scene.]]></VideoLoader>
			<VideoLoader name="section15" icon="step4" enabler="2" url="Scenario1_Video5.f4v" wait="4" autoPlay="false" ><![CDATA[Enroute, the Real-Time Intelligence Console takes a snap shot of the video camera and sends officers an enhanced image of the park and the vicinity of the perpetrator.]]></VideoLoader>
			<VideoLoader name="section16" icon="step4" enabler="5" url="Scenario1_Video6.f4v" wait="5" autoPlay="false" ><![CDATA[Since it’s a city park, a number of cameras capture several angles of the event unfolding in real time, giving the Real-Time Crime Center thorough ability to monitor the situation.]]></VideoLoader>
			<VideoLoader name="section17" icon="step5" enabler="3" url="Scenario1_Video7.f4v" wait="6" autoPlay="false" ><![CDATA[The patrol car uses Automatic License Plate Recognition (ALPR) to scan every vehicle. One plate reveals an outstanding arrest warrant. Now, police have the name and more information of a possible suspect.]]></VideoLoader>
			<VideoLoader name="section18" icon="step3" enabler="7" url="Scenario1_Video8.f4v" wait="4" autoPlay="false" ><![CDATA[The Real-Time Crime Center also verbally conveys all important details via the radio console "MCC7100" to the responding officers.]]></VideoLoader>
			<VideoLoader name="section19" icon="step6" enabler="6" url="Scenario1_Video9.f4v" wait="5" autoPlay="false" ><![CDATA[With the help of Real-Time Crime Center, officers arrive at the scene and are able to correctly anticipate the situation with the help of the advanced information received.]]></VideoLoader>
			<VideoLoader name="section110" icon="step6" enabler="-1" url="Scenario1_Video10.f4v" autoPlay="false" ><![CDATA[They apprehend the suspect without further incident or injury to anyone.]]>
			</VideoLoader>
		</section>
		<section name="INCIDENT RESPONSE">
			<VideoLoader name="section21" icon="step1" enabler="0" url="_RTCC_Scenario2_mov_0.f4v" wait="5" autoPlay="false" ><![CDATA[The 9-1-1 call taker receives a call reporting a protest forming at Main and Smith: “A CROWD IS QUICKLY BUILDING! A LOT OF PUSHING IS GOING ON. SEND POLICE IMMEDIATELY BEFORE SOMEONE GETS HURT.”]]></VideoLoader>
			<VideoLoader name="section22" icon="step1" enabler="9" url="_RTCC_Scenario2_mov_1.f4v" wait="3" autoPlay="false" ><![CDATA[The 9-1-1 call taker records the incident and dispatcher sends police to the scene. As officers are dispatched, the Real-Time Crime Center officer receives an alert letting them know that they need to begin an investigation.]]></VideoLoader>
			<VideoLoader name="section23" icon="step4" enabler="1" url="_RTCC_Scenario2_mov_2.f4v" wait="3" autoPlay="false" ><![CDATA[The location of the incident and all relevant resources such as cameras are plotted on the console map on the Real-Time Crime Center officer’s monitor.]]></VideoLoader>
			<VideoLoader name="section24" icon="step4" enabler="2" url="_RTCC_Scenario2_mov_3.f4v" wait="4" autoPlay="false" ><![CDATA[By accessing the cameras, the Real-Time Crime Center officer views the events unfolding in real-time, from multiple angles.]]></VideoLoader>
			<VideoLoader name="section25" icon="step4" enabler="2" url="_RTCC_Scenario2_mov_4.f4v" wait="4" autoPlay="false" ><![CDATA[The officer identifies a suspicious individual from the video surveillance cameras, takes a snapshot using the Push-a-Snapshot feature and sends it to the responding officer’s vehicle or handheld device.]]></VideoLoader>
			<VideoLoader name="section26" icon="step7" enabler="3" url="_RTCC_Scenario2_mov_5.f4v" wait="5" autoPlay="false" ><![CDATA[The Real-Time Crime Center officer does a query of the license plate, identifies a stolen vehicle and messages the information to the responding officers.]]></VideoLoader>
			<VideoLoader name="section27" icon="step2" enabler="10" url="_RTCC_Scenario2_mov_6.f4v" wait="6" autoPlay="false" ><![CDATA[With the additional information, the responding officers quickly identify the suspect, make an arrest and restore order to the street corner. All relevant information is automatically added to the CAD record as evidence.]]></VideoLoader>
			<VideoLoader name="section28" icon="step6" enabler="-1" url="_RTCC_Scenario2_mov_7.f4v" wait="4" autoPlay="false" ><![CDATA[With the aid of Motorola’s Real-Time Crime Center, police have access to more information to improve their on-scene situational awareness, closing out incidents faster.]]></VideoLoader>
		</section>
		<section name="INVESTIGATIVE ANALYSIS">
			<VideoLoader name="section31" icon="step1" enabler="13" url="RTCC_Scenario3_0.f4v" wait="5" autoPlay="false" ><![CDATA[At a busy train station a suitcase is left unattended. Surveillance video cameras recognize the suspicious item and record the incident as it unfolds.]]></VideoLoader>
			<VideoLoader name="section32" icon="step1" enabler="1" url="RTCC_Scenario3_1.f4v" wait="3" autoPlay="false" ><![CDATA[Analytics identify the suspicious bag, triggering an alarm at the Real-Time Crime Center. There, an officer views the incident unfold on the video feed and determines that it should be investigated quickly.]]></VideoLoader>
			<VideoLoader name="section33" icon="step4" enabler="2" url="RTCC_Scenario3_2.f4v" wait="3" autoPlay="false" ><![CDATA[The Real-Time Crime Center CAD operator officer transmits a snapshot of the suspicious bag, plus the location of the station’s surveillance camera and dispatches a team of nearby officers to respond.]]></VideoLoader>
			<VideoLoader name="section34" icon="step3" enabler="7" url="RTCC_Scenario3_3.f4v" wait="4" autoPlay="false" ><![CDATA[The Real-Time Crime Center operator radios the dispatched officers thorough descriptions of the package and suspect, who is still inside the station and fleeing towards a north exit door.]]></VideoLoader>
			<VideoLoader name="section35" icon="step4" enabler="1" url="RTCC_Scenario3_4.f4v" wait="4" autoPlay="false" ><![CDATA[Upon his exit, a second camera catches a view of the suspect’s face, which is captured in several screen shots and sent to the responding officers. Now they know exactly who and what they’re looking for.]]></VideoLoader>
			<VideoLoader name="section36" icon="step4" enabler="14" url="RTCC_Scenario3_5.f4v" wait="5" autoPlay="false" ><![CDATA[A third camera scans the suspect’s license plate as he speeds away from the scene. The Real-Time Crime Center automatically sends this, any corresponding data, and a voice message to field officers.]]></VideoLoader>
			<VideoLoader name="section37" icon="step1" enabler="0" url="RTCC_Scenario3_6.f4v" wait="6" autoPlay="false" ><![CDATA[In the meantime, the bomb squad quickly arrives at the station, blocks off the platform and contains the    suspicious package.]]></VideoLoader>
			<VideoLoader name="section38" icon="step1" enabler="0" url="RTCC_Scenario3_7.f4v" wait="4" autoPlay="false" ><![CDATA[As this happens, police officers create a strategic multi-block perimeter to surround and confront the suspect.]]></VideoLoader>
			<VideoLoader name="section39" icon="step6" enabler="-1" url="RTCC_Scenario3_8.f4v" wait="5" autoPlay="false" ><![CDATA[Closing in, officers apprehend and arrest the suspect in a nearby parking lot. Thanks to the Real-Time Crime Center, the ordeal ends without any injuries to bystanders, police or the suspect.]]></VideoLoader>
		</section>
	</LoaderMax>
	<LoaderMax name="rtccstills" prependURLs="rtcc_web_assets/images/stills/">
		<section>
			<ImageLoader name="still11" url="Scenario1_Video1.jpg" />
			<ImageLoader name="still12" url="Scenario1_Video2.jpg" />
			<ImageLoader name="still13" url="Scenario1_Video3.jpg" />
			<ImageLoader name="still14" url="Scenario1_Video4.jpg" />
			<ImageLoader name="still15" url="Scenario1_Video5.jpg" />
			<ImageLoader name="still16" url="Scenario1_Video6.jpg" />
			<ImageLoader name="still17" url="Scenario1_Video7.jpg" />
			<ImageLoader name="still18" url="Scenario1_Video8.jpg" />
			<ImageLoader name="still19" url="Scenario1_Video9.jpg" />
			<ImageLoader name="still110" url="Scenario1_Video10.jpg" />
		</section>
		<section>
			<ImageLoader name="still21" url="_RTCC_Scenario2_mov_1.jpg" />
			<ImageLoader name="still22" url="_RTCC_Scenario2_mov_2.jpg" />
			<ImageLoader name="still23" url="_RTCC_Scenario2_mov_3.jpg" />
			<ImageLoader name="still24" url="_RTCC_Scenario2_mov_4.jpg" />
			<ImageLoader name="still25" url="_RTCC_Scenario2_mov_5.jpg" />
			<ImageLoader name="still26" url="_RTCC_Scenario2_mov_6.jpg" />
			<ImageLoader name="still27" url="_RTCC_Scenario2_mov_7.jpg" />
			<ImageLoader name="still28" url="_RTCC_Scenario2_mov_8.jpg" />
		</section>
		<section>
			<ImageLoader name="still31" url="RTCC_Scenario3_1.jpg" />
			<ImageLoader name="still32" url="RTCC_Scenario3_2.jpg" />
			<ImageLoader name="still33" url="RTCC_Scenario3_3.jpg" />
			<ImageLoader name="still34" url="RTCC_Scenario3_4.jpg" />
			<ImageLoader name="still35" url="RTCC_Scenario3_5.jpg" />
			<ImageLoader name="still36" url="RTCC_Scenario3_6.jpg" />
			<ImageLoader name="still37" url="RTCC_Scenario3_7.jpg" />
			<ImageLoader name="still38" url="RTCC_Scenario3_8.jpg" />
			<ImageLoader name="still39" url="RTCC_Scenario3_9.jpg" />
			<ImageLoader name="still310" url="RTCC_Scenario3_0.jpg" />
		</section>
	</LoaderMax>
	<LoaderMax name="enablers" prependURLs="rtcc_web_assets/images/enablers/">
		<enabler title="Real-Time Intelligence Console" group="111" id="1" locx="320" locy="-110" icon="premierone">
			<title><![CDATA[Real-Time Intelligence Console]]></title>
			<longinfo><![CDATA[<img src="rtcc_web_assets/images/empty.png" width="96px" height="83px" />As the foundational element of a Real-Time Crime Center, the Real-Time Intelligence Console (RIC) brings together surveillance video, radio voice and CAD information into an intuitive, multi-function map environment.<br /><br />• Video aggregation from multiple, separate video surveillance management systems<br />• ESRI GIS-based map view of the community showing the location of fixed cameras, in-vehicle DVR cameras and deployed resources from active CAD incidents<br />• Event sensor information such as motion or gun shot detectors and alarms<br />• Real-time video from camera sources including in-vehicle and wearable mobile cameras, with no buffering or delays]]></longinfo>
			<ImageLoader name="enabler1" url="ric.png" />
			<whitepaper>http://www.motorolasolutions.com/web/Business/Products/Software%20and%20Applications/Public%20Sector%20Applications/Public%20Safety%20Applications/Real-time_Intelligence_Console/_Staticfiles/Real-Time_Intelligence_Console_Data_Sheet.pdf</whitepaper>
			<page><![CDATA[http://www.motorolasolutions.com/ric]]></page>
		</enabler>
		<enabler title="Real-Time Video Intelligence" group="111" id="2" locx="320" locy="-100" icon="realtime">
			<title><![CDATA[Real-Time Video Intelligence]]></title>
			<longinfo><![CDATA[<img src="rtcc_web_assets/images/empty.png" width="96px" height="83px" />Real-Time Video Intelligence (RTVI) software delivers high-quality video to and from the patrol car and the command center – and between personnel in the field.<br /><br />In wireless environments, RTVI adjusts to available bandwidth, ensuring that real-time, live video is broadcast at the best possible quality.<br /><br />With its user-friendly interface, RTVI allows cameras to be selected from a list, a map, or an emailed link, accepting video from multiple camera and recorder vendors. Whether it’s a supervisor monitoring another officer’s pursuit from his patrol vehicle, or a SWAT team captain watching building security footage on her handheld, RTVI brings it to them, in real time.]]></longinfo>
			<ImageLoader name="enabler2" url="realtime.png" />
			<whitepaper><![CDATA[http://www.motorola.com/web/Business/Products/Software%20and%20Applications/Public%20Sector%20Applications/Government%20Video%20Applications/REAL_Time-video/Real-Time_Video_Intelligence_Brochure.pdf]]></whitepaper>
			<page><![CDATA[http://www.motorola.com/Business/US-EN/Business+Product+and+Services/Software+and+Applications/Public+Sector+Applications/Government+Video+Applications/Real-Time%20Video%20Intelligence]]></page>
		</enabler>
		<enabler title="Automatic License Plate Recognition" group="100" id="3" locx="320" locy="-210" icon="license">
			<title><![CDATA[Automatic License Plate Recognition]]></title>
			<longinfo><![CDATA[<img src="rtcc_web_assets/images/empty.png" width="96px" height="83px" />Enhance your officers' safety and productivity while maximizing your department's revenue. Automatic License Plate Recognition (ALPR) delivers the ability to read vehicle license plates and reference them against an installed database for rapid identity verification.<br /><br />This license plate recognition system has been used to locate stolen or wanted vehicles and identify parking-ticket scofflaws.<br /><br />This rapidly deployable, scalable solution uses rugged infrared cameras that connect to leading-edge optical character recognition (OCR) technology software, allowing you to conduct surveillance under varied lighting and weather conditions. Captured information is immediately processed, and you are alerted only when a "hit" occurs.]]></longinfo>
			<ImageLoader name="enabler3" url="license.png" />
			<whitepaper><![CDATA[http://www.motorola.com/web/Business/_Documents/Application%20Briefs/Motorola_ALPR_RO-14-2005B.pdf]]></whitepaper>
			<page><![CDATA[http://www.motorola.com/Business/US-EN/Business+Product+and+Services/Software+and+Applications/Public+Sector+Applications/Automatic+License+Plate+Recognition_US-EN]]></page>
		</enabler>
		<enabler title="ShotSpotter" group="100" id="4" locx="320" locy="-210" icon="spotter">
			<title><![CDATA[ShotSpotter<br /><font size="12">Advanced Gunshot Detection</font>]]></title>
			<longinfo><![CDATA[<img src="rtcc_web_assets/images/empty.png" width="125px" height="34px" />When law enforcement responds to an incident, there’s no room to second guess the situation if gunfire is involved – without complete and accurate information, one shot could mean the difference between life or death for police and civilians alike. <br /><br />ShotSpotter® is an advanced gunfire locater utilizing sensors to detect, or “spot,” gunshots through a series of 360-degree, wide-area audio and video surveillance sensors. With ShotSpotter, police won’t learn of a firearm incident through 911 alone; now, law enforcement can hear and view gunfire as it happens, providing them with real-time information and a more successful law enforcement response to gun violence.]]></longinfo>
			<ImageLoader name="enabler4" url="shotspotter.png" />
			<whitepaper>none</whitepaper>
			<page><![CDATA[http://www.shotspotter.com/?gclid=CO736K-WsLECFcyc7Qod-WAAcg]]></page>
		</enabler>
		<enabler title="BriefCam" group="100" id="5" locx="320" locy="-210" icon="briefcam">
			<title><![CDATA[BriefCam]]></title>
			<longinfo><![CDATA[<img src="rtcc_web_assets/images/empty.png" width="125px" height="83px" />Researching hours and hours of surveillance footage can needlessly prolong an investigation when time matters most. With video synopsis technology from BriefCam®, your detectives can condense their review time, plus find and display any event, in only a few minutes.<br /><br />With faster video review results, investigations are expedited. Access and resources are made more efficient – fewer law enforcement personnel are needed, and video storage capacity and costs are greatly reduced.]]></longinfo>
			<ImageLoader name="enabler5" url="briefcam.png" />
			<whitepaper>none</whitepaper>
			<page><![CDATA[http://www.briefcam.com]]></page>
		</enabler>
		<enabler title="Application Integration" group="110" id="6" locx="320" locy="-210" icon="appint">
			<title><![CDATA[Application Integration]]></title>
			<longinfo><![CDATA[<img src="rtcc_web_assets/images/empty.png" width="96px" height="83px" />Deliver the technology and manpower you need to rapidly introduce, update and control access to applications.<br /><br />Your communication systems consist of numerous components, each requiring smart integration to work effectively. We (MSI) have the resources to help you bridge legacy to next generation applications.<br /><br />With our Application Implementation service, you can rest assured that your new and legacy applications will work seamlessly together. The result – faster, more effective response times.]]></longinfo>
			<ImageLoader name="enabler6" url="appint.png" />
			<whitepaper>none</whitepaper>
			<page><![CDATA[http://www.motorolasolutions.com/US-EN/Services/Expertise/Integration+Services]]></page>
		</enabler>
		<enabler title="MCC7100 IP Dispatch Console" group="111" id="7" locx="320" locy="-210" icon="radio">
			<title><![CDATA[MCC7100 IP Dispatch Console]]></title>
			<longinfo><![CDATA[<img src="rtcc_web_assets/images/empty.png" width="96px" height="83px" />Motorola's MCC7100 is a P25-encrypted, voice communications dispatch console allowing law enforcement officials in the field to take command of situations from virtually anywhere, without having to juggle multiple portable radios for communications. <br /><br />As either a fixed or portable solution, the fully interoperable MCC7100 allows on-the-spot coordination with personnel, with the ability to easily monitor and initiate communications from the office, on the road or remotely – during special events, for disaster management, in backup facilities and to increase temporary dispatch capacity. ]]></longinfo>
			<ImageLoader name="enabler7" url="radio.png" />
			<whitepaper>none</whitepaper>
			<page><![CDATA[http://www.motorola.com/Business/US-EN/Business+Product+and+Services/Dispatch/Dispatch+Consoles/MCC+7100]]></page>
		</enabler>
		<enabler title="MVX1000 In-Car Digital Video System" group="010" id="8" locx="320" locy="-210" icon="mvx1000">
			<title><![CDATA[MVX1000 In-Car Digital Video System]]></title>
			<longinfo><![CDATA[<img src="rtcc_web_assets/images/empty.png" width="96px" height="83px" />With a solid-state form to an intuitive user interface, MVX1000 is designed to capture high-quality video in the vehicle while letting you focus on your job.<br /><br />MVX1000 is an in-car and back-end video capture and management solution, combining high-quality video, reliable, ruggedized construction and a smart touch-screen with next generation mission critical functionality to better protect the public and the officer at the scene of an emergency event.<br /><br />In the patrol car (or in multiple vehicles), record and correlate video, audio, and GPS location. At the station, download data to the server – wirelessly, or over a wire. Video, audio, and data streams can be reviewed or exported as evidence when using MVX1000.]]></longinfo>
			<ImageLoader name="enabler8" url="mvx1000.png" />
			<whitepaper>none</whitepaper>
			<page><![CDATA[http://www.motorolasolutions.com/US-EN/Business+Product+and+Services/Software+and+Applications/Public+Sector+Applications/MVX1000]]></page>
		</enabler>
		<enabler title="PremierOne CAD" group="010" id="9" locx="320" locy="-210" icon="premierone">
			<title><![CDATA[PremierOne CAD]]></title>
			<longinfo><![CDATA[<img src="rtcc_web_assets/images/empty.png" width="96px" height="83px" />Dynamic and intuitive, PremierOne™ CAD helps agencies improve response times, efficiently allocate resources and better inform first responders through improved information gathering and situational awareness.<br /><br />PremierOne CAD delivers real-time information into the hands of emergency personnel, with a highly customizable user interface offering quick access to information via a true, location-based, GIS data map.<br /><br />Aided by GPS, this resource management tool displays the exact pinpoint location and identity of mobile units so a more efficient and coordinated response is enabled.]]></longinfo>
			<ImageLoader name="enabler9" url="premierone.png" />
			<whitepaper>none</whitepaper>
			<page><![CDATA[http://www.motorolasolutions.com/US-EN/Business+Product+and+Services/Dispatch/Computer+Aided+Dispatch+%28CAD%29/PremierOne_CAD_US-EN]]></page>
		</enabler>
		<enabler title="PremierOne Records" group="010" id="10" locx="320" locy="-210" icon="premierone">
			<title><![CDATA[PremierOne Records]]></title>
			<longinfo><![CDATA[<img src="rtcc_web_assets/images/empty.png" width="96px" height="83px" />Built on a common platform, PremierOne™ Records captures and secures all records data into a single repository for advanced information sharing, powerful efficiencies and unsurpassed security.<br /><br />Agencies can tailor PremierOne’s efficient data entry methodology to match specific business processes resulting in easily searchable, presentable and shared data across multiple agencies and jurisdictions.<br /><br />PremierOne Records ensures data integrity with class-leading security, auditing and logging functions that provide a “chain of custody” for all records.<br /><br />Agencies experience a lower total cost of ownership through more affordable deployment methods and reduced training needs with PremierOne Records.]]></longinfo>
			<ImageLoader name="enabler10" url="premier.png" />
			<whitepaper>none</whitepaper>		<page><![CDATA[http://www.motorolasolutions.com/US-EN/Business+Solutions/Industry+Solutions/Government/Law+Enforcement/Command+and+Control/PremierOne_Records_US-EN]]></page>
		</enabler>
		<enabler title="Repair Services" group="010" id="11" locx="320" locy="-210" icon="repair">
			<title><![CDATA[Repair Services]]></title>
			<longinfo><![CDATA[<img src="rtcc_web_assets/images/empty.png" width="96px" height="83px" />Today’s IP communications networks are complex, sophisticated, interconnected systems that involve a multitude of components. Staying on top of this latest technology, and maintaining in-house repair operations can place a great burden on commanders tasked with managing their officers and responders. With the investment in equipment and tools, and training needed to keep a dedicated staff of technicians up to speed, a solution is needed. <br /><br />Motorola's expert Repair Services easily keep a department's mobile technology in top shape, ready and available. ]]></longinfo>
			<ImageLoader name="enabler11" url="repair.png" />
			<whitepaper>none</whitepaper>
			<page><![CDATA[http://www.motorolasolutions.com/US-EN/Services/Run/Repair/Infrastructure+Repair]]></page>
		</enabler>
		<enabler title="Vid Sys" group="010" id="12" locx="320" locy="-210" icon="videosys">
			<title><![CDATA[Vid Sys]]></title>
			<longinfo><![CDATA[<img src="rtcc_web_assets/images/empty.png" width="96px" height="83px" />RTCC commanders need the intuitive intelligence that helps them make actionable decisions in the field. The VidSys Physical Security Information Management (PSIM) software platform makes this happen.<br /><br />Connecting video surveillance equipment to legacy alarms, sensors and other infrastructure, PSIM software enables organizations to pro-actively resolve business and security situations in real time. It aids law enforcement in sharing information across multiple jurisdictions, providing responders with the critical details they need when arriving to an incident – in real time. VidSys also makes sure that public safety agencies have the right resources when they need them most.]]></longinfo>
			<ImageLoader name="enabler12" url="vidsys.png" />
			<whitepaper>none</whitepaper>
			<page><![CDATA[http://www.vidsys.com/]]></page>
		</enabler>
		<enabler title="NICE" group="011" id="13" locx="320" locy="-210" icon="nice">
			<title><![CDATA[NICE]]></title>
			<longinfo><![CDATA[<img src="rtcc_web_assets/images/empty.png" width="96px" height="83px" />NICE Systems provides solutions that capture and analyze interactions and transactions, realize intent, and extract and leverage insights to deliver impact in real time to law enforcement agencies.<br /><br />NICE's multidimensional coverage solutions allow the RTCC to conduct surveillance, monitor and track events as they happen, in real time.]]></longinfo>
			<ImageLoader name="enabler13" url="nice.png" />
			<whitepaper>none</whitepaper>
			<page><![CDATA[http://www.nice.com/]]></page>
		</enabler>
		<enabler title="Advanced Messaging Solution" group="001" id="14" locx="320" locy="-210" icon="appint">
			<title><![CDATA[Advanced Messaging Solution]]></title>
			<longinfo><![CDATA[<img src="rtcc_web_assets/images/empty.png" width="96px" height="83px" />By leveraging the Advanced Messaging Solution, the Real-Time Crime Center officers can quickly send messages directly to any device through the radio network.<br /><br />With access to this information, first responders are able to make on-the-spot decisions, freeing air time for critical voice communications.]]></longinfo>
			<ImageLoader name="enabler14" url="advanced.png" />
			<whitepaper>none</whitepaper>
			<page><![CDATA[http://www.motorolasolutions.com/US-EN/Business+Product+and+Services/Software+and+Applications/Two-Way+Radio+Applications/ASTRO_25_Software_Applications/ASTRO_25_ADVANCED_MESSAGING_SOLUTION_US-EN]]></page>
		</enabler>		
	</LoaderMax>
		<LoaderMax name="audio" prependURLs="rtcc_web_assets/audios/">
		<section>
			<MP3Loader name="audio11" url="RTCC_Scenario1_1.mp3" autoPlay="false" />
			<MP3Loader name="audio12" url="RTCC_Scenario1_2.mp3" autoPlay="false" />
			<MP3Loader name="audio13" url="RTCC_Scenario1_3.mp3" autoPlay="false" />
			<MP3Loader name="audio14" url="RTCC_Scenario1_4.mp3" autoPlay="false" />
			<MP3Loader name="audio15" url="RTCC_Scenario1_5.mp3" autoPlay="false" />
			<MP3Loader name="audio16" url="RTCC_Scenario1_6.mp3" autoPlay="false" />
			<MP3Loader name="audio17" url="RTCC_Scenario1_7.mp3" autoPlay="false" />
			<MP3Loader name="audio18" url="RTCC_Scenario1_8.mp3" autoPlay="false" />
			<MP3Loader name="audio19" url="RTCC_Scenario1_9.mp3" autoPlay="false" />
			<MP3Loader name="audio110" url="RTCC_Scenario1_10.mp3" autoPlay="false" />
		</section>
		<section>
			<MP3Loader name="audio21" url="RTCC_Scenario2_1.mp3" autoPlay="false" />
			<MP3Loader name="audio22" url="RTCC_Scenario2_2.mp3" autoPlay="false" />
			<MP3Loader name="audio23" url="RTCC_Scenario2_3.mp3" autoPlay="false" />
			<MP3Loader name="audio24" url="RTCC_Scenario2_4.mp3" autoPlay="false" />
			<MP3Loader name="audio25" url="RTCC_Scenario2_5.mp3" autoPlay="false" />
			<MP3Loader name="audio26" url="RTCC_Scenario2_6.mp3" autoPlay="false" />
			<MP3Loader name="audio27" url="RTCC_Scenario2_7.mp3" autoPlay="false" />
			<MP3Loader name="audio28" url="RTCC_Scenario2_8.mp3" autoPlay="false" />
		</section>
		<section>
			<MP3Loader name="audio31" url="RTCC_Scenario3_1.mp3" autoPlay="false" />
			<MP3Loader name="audio32" url="RTCC_Scenario3_2.mp3" autoPlay="false" />
			<MP3Loader name="audio33" url="RTCC_Scenario3_3.mp3" autoPlay="false" />
			<MP3Loader name="audio34" url="RTCC_Scenario3_4.mp3" autoPlay="false" />
			<MP3Loader name="audio35" url="RTCC_Scenario3_5.mp3" autoPlay="false" />
			<MP3Loader name="audio36" url="RTCC_Scenario3_6.mp3" autoPlay="false" />
			<MP3Loader name="audio37" url="RTCC_Scenario3_7.mp3" autoPlay="false" />
			<MP3Loader name="audio38" url="RTCC_Scenario3_8.mp3" autoPlay="false" />
			<MP3Loader name="audio39" url="RTCC_Scenario3_9.mp3" autoPlay="false" />
		</section>
	</LoaderMax>
</rtcc>